BARTOSZ MYLKA

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER















ABOUT

I have been passionate about IT for many years. Lately, the field of coding particularly caught my interest. That's why recently I have decided to retrain myself at Coders Lab. In the near future I hope to combine my communication and language skills with my newly acquired coding skills.

TRAINING

Coders Lab

03/2017 - 04/2017

Bootcamp become Front-End Developer: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, ECMAScript 6, React, RWD, Sass, Git.

CONTACT



+48 504 505 230



bmylka@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/bartosz-mylka



github.com/BartekMy

LANGUAGE

German - native speaker Polish - near native / fluent English - very good command

HOBBIES

SKILLS

IT Team player

Coding Strong written and verbal Reading communications skills

Sport / Fitness MS Office

Languages Driving licence Class B

EXPERIENCE

Becton Dickinson Polska Sp. z o.o.

01/2016 - 02/2017

Customer Service Complaints Handling Representative for the GSA markets (Germany, Switzerland and Austria)

Irkutsk State Linguistic University, Irkutsk, Russia

09/2015 - 09/2015

Internship as a teacher of German language

Stadtwerke Zittau GmbH, Zittau, Germany

09/2014 - 10/2014

Interpreter (Polish – German, German – Polish)

Bernd Jorkisch GmbH & Co. KG, Daldorf, Germany

11/2006 - 06/2011

Dispatcher - Planning and organizing international transports (Forwarding and Logistics Services). Working together with several forwarders from Germany and Poland.

EDUCATION

Hochschule Zittau / Görlitz - University of Applied Sciences

09/2011 - 11/2015

BA in translation English / Polish
Bachelor thesis: Software localization - General
theoretical introduction and the practical
implementation on the basis of chosen digital games

Oświadczam, że wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych w celu przeprowadzenia procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 29.08.1997r. o ochronie danych osobowych Dz. U. Nr 133, poz. 883).